### PHUAD ADEBOWALE

+234-814-790-2542 temidayo26j@gmail.com

131 Adeyemo Akapo Omole Phase 1, Lagos Nigeria.

In: Phuad-Adebowale,
Portfolio Website
Git Repository

#### **PROFILE**

Highly skilled Software Engineer a couple years worth of experience in tech space and early in the field of being a writer and web-designer. A strong interest in growing all specified expertise. Proficient at communicating. Familiar with modern JavaScript frameworks like React also familiar with nuxt Vue and the skill of project coordination. Strong suites are communication skills, conflict resolution with a proactive attitude towards problem solving.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Tech Support , Ministry of Tourism, Arts and Culture** ikeja Lagos

February 2022 - Present

- Associate Project Coordinator on implementing Biometric attendance system amongst other project by Implementing third-party technology systems and configuring and integrating existing infrastructure.
- Part of the advisory board for Ministry of Tourism Art and Culture web platform.
- Facilitate training for staffs and administrative members and support staff of a little over 200 staff members.
- Provided ongoing support and maintenance for the implemented systems, including troubleshooting software and hardware systems as needed.

## IT lead, Adebouge Holdings Adebouge Holding, Houston, Texas USA

Dec. 2021 - Present

- Building and maintaining the <u>company's platform</u>, including adding new features, updating content, and fixing any issues that arise.
- Testing the website to ensure that it is compatible with different browsers and devices.
- Keeping up-to-date with new web technologies and techniques, and continually improving the company's web presence.

### **Server-room assistant**

Ministry of Science, Ikeja, Lagos Jan 2020 — Apr 2021

- Maintenance of the company's server room, including organising cables, installing new hardware, and performing regular checks on equipment.
- Assisted with the setup and configuration of servers and other equipment as needed, and Responded to technical issues and provided troubleshooting support for server-related problems.
- Collaborated with the IT team to ensure the proper functioning of all server room equipment, while adhering to industry standards.
- Managed the replacement, crimping, and testing of cables to improve the network infrastructure and increase network speed and reliability by 20%

### **EDUCATION**

Babcock University, Ilishan-Ogun State ,2021 BSc Studied Computer Science

Aptech , Allen Lagos State ,2016 **Web Development** 

### **SKILLS**

Experience with modern JavaScript frameworks like React Strong problem-solving skills Excellent writing and verbal communication skills Proactive and self-driven work ethic